Hello friends, welcome to the
Technical YouTube Hindi channel. Today in this
video we will learn
how to do third party insurance for two wheeler from ICC Lobot. The
entire process will be seen in today's video
from the middle of CSC. So, as you
go to CSC, you have to go as if the
dashboard of our CSC Teacher So
portal is open, then we go directly here to the
insurance section. As soon as you
click on the insurance icon,
you have to go here, Motor Third Party.
Click on it. There are many
companies here, so we do not have to search much.
As soon as we go to search here
and write like this, it will
appear at the top, you will see Motor Third
Part.
As soon as you click, it will appear. You will see
some such interface on the ICC portal.
Click on the portal.
After clicking Chitrakoot, you will go to the new
portal. Here you have to enter the
registration number, that is, whatever your bike number is.
After filing it here,
you have to click on Get RTO Details. Like, if you
click on Get RTO Details, everything will happen
automatically, after that you will have to click on Gate here,
but  Let me
show you by clicking on the RTO details. As soon as we click on Get RTO,
some details like model etc. will be uploaded here, nothing needs to be changed.
If the company etc. given to you is
not matching automatically, you
can also fill it manually. Click on manufacturing date
etc. As soon as you
click on Get, your
premium amount will be shown. If you
want to make some changes in it, you can do it.
But we have Mantra which is a third party, after
one fourth three, the
rights came for Rs. 45. So let's click on profit and
because of that, now we will click on proceed.
Here your engine number
and chassis number will be automatically uploaded and above this
your details will be uploaded like which
RTO your bike is registered with, some other details will be uploaded
and here the vehicle description, there is
no need to fill it, go down,
you KYC, this is most important,
you have to click on this only, so let's
do KYC first, after that
go to the next level, you have to do
ICC from the middle of one level.
Like you have a very normal Aadhar
card or PAN card, whatever you have, you have to
file all the details, after that you have to click on submit,
so let's do KYC through our Aadhar card,
after filing the details we click on submit,
as soon as we click on submit, here the
details and address will be taken from your Aadhar card
and all the things will be filled here,
after that click on proceed here, as soon as we
click on proceed,
whatever address was in your Aadhar card will be filled here
automatically, some things have to be
filled, like here second
address, land mark and here
you file it, otherwise none is necessary, it is
optional and here
after filling all the things, you have to click on net propose, then
you will be able to open
and your policy will be created and generated, so in
this way you can
create insurance, you can generate the policy,
you must have understood how to create a two wheeler policy.